In the last lesson we talked very importantly about how to inquire how to get information from people
在上一课中，我们非常重要地讨论了如何查询如何从人们那里获取信息
that we don't know especially on the phone.
我们不知道，尤其是在电话中。
In this lesson we're going to talk about something that's also very important but more personal more
在本课中，我们将讨论一些也非常重要但更个人化的东西
about what we do.
关于我们做什么。
We're going to talk about your routine now your routine is what you usually do every day.
我们现在要谈谈你的日常生活，你的日常生活就是你每天通常做的事情。
That's your routine and your routine maybe includes going to work what you do when you get up and maybe
那是你的例行公事，你的例行公事可能包括你起床时的工作，也许
what you do on the weekend.
你周末做什么。
You can have a routine for different kinds of things for example you can say my workout routine you
你可以为不同类型的事情制定一个例程，例如你可以说我的锻炼例程你
can say my travel routine you can say my weekend routine so in general routine means just what you usually
可以说我的旅行例程 你可以说我的周末例程 所以一般来说例程就是你通常的意思
do unless you say something more specific in front of it like workout routine travel routine work routine
除非你在它前面说一些更具体的东西，比如锻炼例行旅行例行工作例程
in general routine means what we do on a normal day.
一般来说，例行公事是指我们在正常的一天所做的事情。
We're going to talk about some useful phrases that we can use as well as some important words that we
我们将讨论一些我们可以使用的有用短语以及一些我们可以使用的重要词
need to know when we're describing what we do our routine and we're going to talk about the things that
需要知道什么时候我们在描述我们的日常工作，我们将谈论那些
we have to do for example at work our responsibilities.
例如，我们必须在工作中履行我们的职责。
How do we introduce our responsibilities when people ask you about yourself.
当人们问起您自己时，我们如何介绍我们的责任。
You need to be able to explain what it is that you do every day right.
你需要能够解释你每天都做对了什么。
What is your job exactly.
你的工作到底是什么。
What do you have to do in your job.
你在工作中必须做什么。
And then finally we're going to look at a real example.
最后我们来看一个真实的例子。
We're going to look at a routine.
我们将看一个例程。
It's gonna be a little bit long.
它会有点长。
Kind of like a story but hopefully it can give you a feeling for how people will describe the things
有点像一个故事，但希望它能让你了解人们如何描述事物
they have to do on a normal day because it's very important to be able to do that and it often comes
他们必须在正常的一天做，因为能够做到这一点非常重要，而且经常会发生
up in conversation.
在谈话中。
What did you do yesterday.
你昨天做了什么。
Oh yesterday I blah blah blah blah blah blah blah.
哦，昨天我胡说八道。
And then you say your routine so let's start with some phrases.
然后你说你的例行公事，让我们从一些短语开始。